So like when I first when I first came
here to do a fringe show in this room
Which is three years ago and the night
before my first show I
was supposed to come here and do a
tech rehearsal.
I got no idea what fucking tech
rehearsal was I'm like what like if I
come on
to this tech rehearsal What are they
gonna ask me like they're gonna ask me
questions
about the lighting doesn't mean I'm
not really gonna know I'm like an
idiot and
I was really really fretting about it
and like I'm not saying I would have
done
this But there was like part me was
thinking well, maybe I just won't do
this
show then like if I have to go to this
tech rehearsal, I won't just I just
won't
do this show and It was kind of
because it was humiliating.
It was just me kind of being asked to
do something I didn't know how to do
and
of course I turned up and they said
how do you want your lights?
And I was like like a stand -up stage
and they were like, yeah, what you
mean
like that? I was like, yeah, and they
said like do you want to play some
music
cuz like yeah, that was it All right,
so that kind of wasn't a big deal